他会付账的
He's picking up our tab.
好极了
Excellent.
下次我们改在萨克斯的鞋店见面好了
Next time, let's meet in the shoe department at Saks.
我他妈才不管你的招牌上写什么
I don't care what your fucking title is.
- 这是经理的决定 - 你那群混账朋友
- It's house manager. - Your dirtbag friends come in
来待在我部门里 指手画脚
and sit in my section, they got to order.
他们不会指手画脚 他们只是经理的客人
They don't got to order, they're guests of the house manager.
那就请他们去别的部门待着
Then sit them in another section.
可是只有一个部门 就是你的那个啊
There's only one section, your section.
我他妈不干了 苏西
I fucking quit, Susie.
那我会心碎的
I'm heartbroken.
- 你好 煤油灯 - 嗨 我是米琪
- Gaslight. - Hey, it's Midge.
我留了一堆消息 让杰基给你
I left a bunch of messages for you with Jackie.
- 他给你了吗 - 等下
- Did he give them to you? - Hang on.
杰基 你那有没有米琪留给我的什么消息
Jackie, did you have messages from Midge for me?
- 大概有吧 - 混蛋 - 混蛋
- Possibly. -Asshole. - Asshole.